Man, how long is Jaggy gonna sleep?
إلى متى سينام ذلك المسنّن
We've got a problem!
لدينا مشكلة
Inmate Eustass Kid escaped!
السجين يوستاس كيد قد هرب
What?!
ماذا؟
Unbe-lick-able.
يا للحظ العاثر-بيرورين
Mama just had to fall off at the top of the waterfall!
لم تسقط ماما من السفينة إلا حين وصلنا قمة الشلال
King's aerial defense makes it impossible to get back up there...
لا يسعنا العودة إلى هناك في ظل حراسة كينغ من السماء
It's a miracle the Queen Mama Chanter didn't capsize...
إنّ عدم انقلاب سفينة كوين ماما شانتر بعد سقوطها من ذلك الارتفاع لمعجزة حقًّا
So, we just wait here or what?
أخبروني، ألا يسعنا سوى الانتظار؟
For now.
حاليًّا نعم
If we're thrown overboard, anyone with powers will be incapacitated.
نحن أصحاب قدرات الفواكه سنكون عاجزين إن سقطنا من السفينة
No! Then, Mama sank into the sea?!
محال، أيعني هذا أنّ ماما غرقت؟
Don't worry!
لا داعي للقلق
Speaking of miracles...
هذه معجزة أيضًا
According to Mama's vivre card, she survived!
تُظهر فيفر كارد ماما بأنها ما زالت حية ترزق
Great! So she's alive!
هذا مطمئن، إنها حية
But then, where is she?!
ولكن أين عساها تكون الآن؟
The Beast Pirates undoubtedly fished her out and are already holding her captive.
ألا يدل هذا على احتمالية أنّ قراصنة الوحوش انتشلوها وأسروها؟
Mama and Kaido used to be crewmates,
ماما وكايدو كانا رفيقين في طاقم واحد
but they've grown adversarial since becoming Emperors.
لكنهما الآن عدوان متنافسان بصفتهما من الأباطرة الأربعة
He'll definitely kill her.
سيقتلها بلا ريب
What?! Then what's gonna happen to us?!
ماذا؟ ماذا سيحلّ بنا بعدها؟
Lickity-listen...
بيرورين
The Big Mom Pirates will become...
...سيصبح طاقم قراصنة بيغ مام
the lickity Perospero Pirates!
طاقم قراصنة بيروسبيرو
Hey, what's the big idea, Peros?!
مهلًا، عمّ تتحدث يا أخي بيروس؟
Our next captain has to be Katakuri!
القبطان التالي يجب أن يكون كاتاكوري
Don't you give a lick about seniority?!
الأولوية للأكبر سنًّا-بيرورين
Nonsense! Merit is more important!
لا تتحامق، الأولوية للجدارة
The eldest son should lead!
القيادة من نصيب الابن الأكبر
Do you want me to summon my genie?! Don't think I won't!
أتريد أن أستدعي الجني؟
Cut it out!
توقفا
Don't just assume she's gonna die!
لا تفترضا أنّ ماما قُتلت
Never underestimate Mama, you morons.
لا تستخفّا ماما يا مغفلان
Big Mom?
بيغ مام؟
Yes, she's a super strong person from overseas!
أجل، إنها امرأة قوية من خارج البلاد
This sharkodile is a very docile and sweet animal!
هذا الوانيزامي مطيع ولطيف للغاية
You had to hit it twice to tame it!
لأنكِ ضربتيه مرتين لترويضه
Wait! Why in the world would you need to go to Udon with this Big Mom person?!
مهلًا، لماذا ستذهبون إلى مقاطعة أودون مع المدعوة بيغ مام؟
Because she's going to help us save Big Bro!
لأنها ستساعدنا بإنقاذ أخي الكبير
I-I do not follow!
لـ-لم أفهم
Get back here, Otama! I need more details!
عودي حالًا يا أوتاما، أريد معرفة التفاصيل
Sir Kin'emon instructed me to guard Lord Momonosuke closely!
طلب كينيمون-دونو مني حماية مومونسكي-ساما
It'll be all right, Master!
لا داعي للقلق يا معلمي
As a kunoichi, I will protect Momo at any cost!
سأحرص على حماية مومو-كن بصفتي كونويتشي
Who...? Who...?!
...من... من
Who's a kunoichi?! Your skills are middling at best!
من تقصدين بالكونويتشي؟ لستِ مؤهلة لهذا المسمى بعد
Stop being so reckless and return immediately, Otama!
لا تتصرفي بحماقة وعودي حالًا يا أوتاما
Sir Hitetsu, we have already departed.
هيتيتسو-دونو، نحن توجهنا إلى هناك سلفًا
What?! No, Lady Okiku...!
ماذا؟ كلا يا أوكيكو-دونو
Return this instant!
عودوا حالًا
Say "hi" to Komachiyo and the others!
أبلغ تحياتي إلى كوماتشيو والبقية
By the way, did I hear you correctly when you said "Big Mom" earlier?
"بالمناسبة، سمعتكِ توًّا تقولين "بيغ مام
That sounds familiar...
يبدو مألوفًا
Forget about that, Olin!
لا تكترثي له يا أولين
Anyway, the people at Okobore Town were so nice.
على أي حال، سكان بلدة أوكوبوري كانوا كرماء معي
I was a stranger to them, and I don't even know my own name,
رغم أنهم يجهلون هويتي
but that lady still treated me to that sweet and delicious oshiruko...
إلا أنّ تلك المرأة أكرمتني بطبق الأوشيروكو اللذيذ
The hat hasn't spoken at all. Did it also lose its memory?
تلك القبعة الناطقة لم تتحدث بتاتًا، هل فقدت ذاكرتها أيضًا؟
That reminds me...
...تذكرت الآن
I wanna have some more oshiruko soon.
أريد تناول الأوشيروكو بسرعة
Don't look at me when you say that!
لا تنظري إلي حين تقولين هذا
I can't help it. You're so cute I could eat you up...
ظرافتك هي من تجعلني أرغب بأكلك
I'm not food!
أنا لست طعامًا
You're really pushing yourself, Momo!
إنك تتدرب بجد يا مومو-كن
I am at the center of this conflict! I must remain sharp!
سأشارك في المعركة، لذا يجب أن أكون مستعدًا
SNATCH!
سوناتشي
Oh, sorry! I apologize!
اعذرني، أستميحك عذرًا
Say, why do you keep yelling "SNATCH"?
بالمناسبة، ما معنى "سوناتشي" التي صرخت بها توًّا؟
Saying SNATCH is really invigorating!
سوناتشي؟ إنها كلمة تمنح المرء الطاقة
SNATCH!
سوناتشي
SNATCH! SNATCH! SNATCH!
سوناتشي، سوناتشي، سوناتشي
You're right! I feel full of energy!
معك حق، تدفقت طاقة كبيرة داخلي
Right? Okay then!
حقًّا؟ عظيم
– SNATCH! SNATCH! SNATCH!
سوناتشي، سوناتشي، سوناتشي
Stop, both of you!
توقفا رجاءً
Why, Kiku?
ما الأمر يا كيكو؟
Where did you learn that word?
من أين تعلمت هذه الكلمة؟
It is a rallying cry foreign swordsmen use!
إنها كلمة يصرخ بها المبارزين من خارج البلاد
I learned it from Zorojuro!
تعلمتها من زوروجورو
He said it's a lucky word that lifts your spirit when courage is lost.
قال إنها بمثابة تميمة تشحذ همّة المبارز وتشجعه
Well, this one forbids its use!
إذًا أنا أمنعك من نطق هذه الكلمة
What?! How come?!
ماذا؟ لماذا؟
It could be a coincidence,
قد تكون مجرد صدفة
but it also exists as a battle cry from an old Kuri dialect.
ولكن ثمة كلمة مشابهة لها في لهجة كوري القديمة
Its implications are inappropriate for you.
ولا يليق بك قولها يا مومونوسكي-ساما
What?! Come on!
ماذا؟ هذا ليس عدلًا
No!
لا تجادل
But it's really invigorating.
إنها مجرد كلمة تمنح الطاقة
No means no!
قلت لا يعني لا
I'm hungry. Aren't we at Udon yet?
أنا جائعة، ألم نصل إلى أودون بعد؟
I'm so hungry I could...
...أنا أتضور جوعًا
Don't look at me when you're drooling!
أخبرتكِ ألّا تنظري إلي بينما يسيل لعابك
Unfortunately, we are still far from Udon, Olin.
بصراحة يا أولين-سان، لا تزال مقاطعة أودون بعيدة
Is that right?!
حقًّا؟
This is a rough map of Wano.
هذه خريطة مبسطة لبلاد وانو
The six regions of the country all have distinct climates and are divided by rivers.
تتضمن بلاد وانو 6 مقاطعات بمناخات مختلفة يفصل بينها نهر طويل
This is...
...هذا
Shinobu's five color rice signal... It says to check near the well...
غوشكيماي؟ لا بد أنها شينوبو
Is that where they are?!
هل هم هناك؟
I am relieved that you are all still alive!
سعيدٌ بكونكم جميعًا بخير
Orochi's men will not venture out this far.
لن يتكبّد أتباع أوروتشي عناء المجيء إلى هنا
The murder of Oiran Komurasaki was quite shocking.
لم أتصور أن تُقتل الأويران الشهيرة كوموراساكي
And now the Flower Capital is in an uproar.
فعلًا، كان لهذا الخبر أصداء واسعة في عاصمة الزهور
Seriously, she was just standing up to Orochi. How could he kill her so mercilessly?!
ولكن كيف سوّلت له نفسه قتلها لمجرد أنها عارضت أوروتشي؟
Samurai are scary...
الساموراي مرعبون
Napping Kyoshiro was the one who cut her down.
الرجل الذي قطع كوموراساكي هو كيوشيرو الناعس
Kyoshiro? I am unfamiliar with that name.
كيوشيرو؟ لم أسمع بهذا الاسم من قبل
Twenty years ago, Wano's greatest yakuza boss...
...قبل عشرين سنة، أعظم زعيم ياكوزا في بلاد وانو كان يُدعى
was Hyogoro the Flower.
هيوغورو الزهرة
What a colorful name.
يا له من اسم رنّان
Boss Hyogoro valued honor and championed the weak;
...الزعيم هيوغورو الذي يُكرم المحتاجين ويساعد الضعفاء
he would never have done something so heartless.
ما كان ليرتكب فعلةً شنيعة كهذه
Napping Kyoshiro... What a horrible man.
كيوشيرو الناعس... يا لفظاعته من رجل
Maybe we shouldn't have taken Otoko back to Kyoshiro's pleasure hall.
يسرني أننا لم نُعِد أوتوكو-تشان إلى منطقة الملذات التي يديرها
Even though she upset the shogun,
رغم أنها أغضبت الشوغن
I have my doubts whether this Kyoshiro will go after a child...
يستحيل أن يسعى كيوشيرو خلف مجرد طفلة
But this guy offed his brothel's most popular woman!
ولكنه قتل الأويران التي تُعد أشهر محظية في بيته للدعارة
It worries me.
ينتابني القلق
Let's head back to the Flower Ca–
...لنعد إلى عاصمة الزهور
It's chilly, isn't it?
أتشعرين بالبرد؟
Nice and warm! Thanks, Shinobu!
إنه دافئ، شكرًا يا شينوبو-تشان
Folks, if we're going back to the Flower Capital,
يا رفاق، إن كنا سنعود إلى عاصمة الزهور
why not rest our weary bones at a bathhouse?
ما رأيكم بالاستحمام لنريح عظامنا المرهقة؟
A bath sounds good!
حمام ساخن؟ فكرة رائعة
That's right. We can freshen ourselves up.
فعلًا، نحتاج إلى الانتعاش
We'd have to sneak in with disguises. Orochi regulates hot water and drinking water.
علينا التنكر، فأوروتشي يسيطر على مصادر المياه الساخنة والنقية
In the Flower Capital, every single aspect of life is controlled.
إذْ يتحكم في جميع احتياجات الحياة لسكان عاصمة الزهور
But first, I would like to hear what information you have collected so far, Lady Orobi.
قبل ذلك يا أوروبي-دونو، أودّ سماع المعلومات التي اكتشفتها حتى الآن
Unfortunately, all I've collected so far is...
أشعر بالإحباط لقلّة المعلومات التي اكتشفتها
what time Orochi will wake up on the day of the battle,
فقط عرفت موعد استيقاظ أوروتشي في يوم المعركة
the offerings that they will take to Onigashima,
والهدايا التي سيأخذونها إلى أونيغاشيما
Kaido's favorite food and how his crew is organized,
وطعام كايدو المفضل والتسلسل القيادي لجيشه
the number of soldiers and weapons...
وعدد الجنود والأسلحة
That is a lot!
هذا كثير
By the way, I discovered a poneglyph.
بالمناسبة، وجدت بونغليف
It wasn't a red one though...
لكنه لم يكن أحمر
Really?!
حقًّا؟
You sure are lucky with those stones, Bonekichi!
إنك محظوظ فعلًا في إيجاد الأحجار أيها العظمي-كيتشي
It was behind a reinforced door in the basement.
كان داخل غرفة لها باب فولاذي في القبو
It was a strange room full of wooden dolls.
غرفة غريبة مليئة بدمى خشبية
That means the lode poneglyph needed to reach Laugh Tale must be on Onigashima.
هذا يعني أنّ بونغليف الطريق الذي سيقودنا إلى لافتيل قد يكون في أونيغاشيما كما توقعت
Onigashima, huh?
أونيغاشيما؟
Mm-hmm. With this much information, we can consider the mission a success.
أجل، بفضل كل هذه المعلومات، يمكننا القول إنّ المهمة تكللت بالنجاح
Now, Orobi and Onami...
والآن يا أوروبي-سان وأونامي-سان
let's go to a bathhouse to rest up and see some panties!
لنذهب للاستحمام ورؤية ملابسكما الداخلية
You'd stand out too much!
لن ترافقنا بسبب مظهرك المُلفت للانتباه
Breaking news!
أخبار عاجلة، أخبار عاجلة
The Flower Capital's top idol, Oiran Komurasaki,
...محبوبة الشعب في عاصمة الزهور الأويران كوموراساكي
was cut down by Boss Kyoshiro at the shogun's banquet!
قتلها الزعيم كيوشيرو في مأدبة الشوغن
You can read about it here!
مزيد من التفاصيل تجدونها هنا
Komurasaki my love!
كوموراساكي-تشوان
How could this happen?!
لماذا ماتت؟
What's with the wailing? You barely even saw her once.
لماذا تبكي؟ لم ترها سوى مرة واحدة
The world lost a true beauty, dumbass!
موت جميلة مثلها خسارة للعالم أجمع يا أحمق
The funeral will be held tomorrow.
ستقام الجنازة غدًا
You're being insensitive!
ألا تملك ذرّة مشاعر؟
The raid suit...
...البذلة القتالية
Do you think Orobi and the others got caught?
أتظنون أنّ أوروبي والبقية قد قُبض عليهم؟
I'm worried. Should I try to contact them by smart snail?
أشعر بالقلق عليهم، هل اتصل بهم عبر الحلزون الذكي؟
What do you think, Sanji?
ما رأيك يا سانجي؟
The power of invisibility...
القدرة على الاختفاء
I guess I have to try it there...
ينبغي لي تجربتها هناك
Hey, Sanji!
سانجي
In the women's bath!
في حمام النساء
Oh, yeah, you're right!
أ-أجل، صحيح
By the way, Traf, is there any word on Udon and Luffytaro?
بالمناسبة يا تراو، ألم يُكتب خبر عن مقاطعة أودون أو لوفيتارو؟
Yeah, he's probably ready to start a riot by now!
صحيح، أراهن أنّ صبره نفد وهرب من السجن
For sure! I can't wait to see him again!
معك حق، أتحرّق شوقًا لرؤيته مجددًا
There's nothing on Straw Hat...
...لا أخبار عن قبعة القش-يا
Wait...
مهلًا
Eustass?!
يوستاس-يا؟
"You..." What?! "You" like the women's bath?!
هل قلت "يويا"؟ أتقصد حمام نساء؟
Oh, you mean that guy's in Wano?!
لا، أقصد هل ذلك الشخص في بلاد وانو أيضًا؟
Since his ally Hawkins is here, it's no wonder that he's here, too...
ما دام حليفه هوكينز هنا، فلا عجب في وجود كيد أيضًا
It seems he was being held at the prison in Udon... and then escaped.
لكنه كان مسجونًا في أودون ثم هرب
Escaped?!
هرب؟
Hey, what about Luffy?!
ماذا عن لوفي؟
I think something big is happening in Udon.
يبدو أنّ مقاطعة أودون ستشهد حدثًا آخر
By the way...
...الأهم
where's the bathhouse?
أيعرف أحدكم أين حمام النساء؟
Dammit! Give it a rest already!
لا وقت لأفكارك هذه يا لعين
You weren't listening at all!
لم تُنصت لحديثنا أصلًا
– You moron!
أيها الوغد
Hey, wait!
مهلًا
I'm worried.
أشعر بالقلق، ذهب بيبو والآخرين للاستكشاف ولم يعودوا بعد
Let's hope it isn't more trouble.
آمل ألّا نواجه مزيدًا من المشكلات
That's gross!
مقرف
Hey, you!
يا هذا
I need to ask you somethin'.
أريد أن أطرح عليك سؤالًا
What?!
ماذا؟
As you may have heard, the prisoner Eustass Kid escaped!
كما تعلم، هرب السجين يوستاس كيد
I bet you know somethin'.
لا بدّ أنك تعرف شيئًا
That reeks!
مقرف
It's been so long since I've had this much to eat...
لم أتناول مثل هذه الكمية منذ مدة
I am in your debt, Sir Straw Hat!
ممتن لك يا فتى قبعة القش
I will... I will cherish every bite.
سأتناولها... سأتناولها بكل امتنان
Hey!
أنت
Let me have some!
أعطني بعضًا منها
Those dumplings look delicious!
تبدو هذه الدانغو لذيذة
I'm sayin' that...
...أنا أقول
you had to have somethin' to do with Kid's escape!
أنت لك علاقة بهروب كيد، صحيح؟
You guys were always talking!
فقد كنتما تتحدثان كثيرًا
His spit really stinks.
بصاقه ذو رائحة مقرفة
Stinks?! Are you mocking me?!
مقرفة؟ أتسخر مني؟
Don't forget you're wearing seastone cuffs!
لا تنسَ أنك مقيّد بالحجر البحري
Anyway, it's only a matter of time before he gets caught!
ولكن سيُقبض عليه عاجلًا أم آجلًا
He clearly didn't think this jailbreak through.
لم تكن خطة هروبه مُحكمة
The moron still had his seastone cuffs on,
فالأحمق ما يزال مقيدًا بالحجر البحري
so he won't get far before he's hunted down and punished!
لذا سيُقبض عليه وينال عقابًا شديدًا
Cut it out! Your spit seriously smells!
توقف، إنك تبصق حين تتكلم أيها المقرف
You're really gonna keep testin' me?!
أيعقل أنك تعارضني؟
You need a refresher on the rules?!
أتريد مني تذكيرك بالعواقب؟
♪ Cross us once, lose your arms! ♪
سنبتر ذراعاك المرة الأولى
♪ Cross us twice, lose your legs! ♪
سنبتر ساقاك في المرة الثانية
♪ Cross us thrice, lose your life! ♪
ستُعدم في المرة الثالثة
Idiot!
أيها الأحمق
You guys shouldn't screw with us!
لا يجدر بكم معارضتنا
Stop hurting old man Hyo! You're killing him!
توقف عن ضرب العجوز هيو وإلا سيموت
Rules are rules. If you can't keep up, you should die!
القوانين مقدسة، ومن يخالفها سيموت
These millet dumplings... are precious...
...الكيبي دانغو الثمينة
Don't you agree?
ألستُ محقًّا؟
The dumplings...!
...الدانغو
The rules say you can only eat what you earn by working.
ينص القانون على منح السجين الطعام مقابل عمله
If you can't work, you starve to death!
من لا يستطيع العمل، مصيره الموت جوعًا
Isn't that right, old man?!
ألا توافقني أيها العجوز؟
Hey! You think you're getting away?!
مهلًا، أتحاول الهرب مني؟
Since you can't work,
بما أنه اتضح عجزك عن العمل
how did you get so many food tickets?!
فلماذا تملك كثيرًا من إيصالات الطعام؟
Who gave them to you?!
من أعطاك إياها؟
Dumplings...
...الدانغو
My precious dumplings...
...الدانغو الثمينة
You greedy old geezer!
أيها العجوز الجشع
So good!
لذيذة
What do you think you're doing?!
ماذا تفعل؟
You have no right to eat anything!
لا يحق لك تناول هذا الطعام
No work? No dumplings!
لا تأكل الدانغو إن كنت لا تعمل
Spit it out, you decrepit old coot!
ابصقها، ابصقها أيها العجوز اللعين
I won't spit them out...
لن أبصقها
Sir Straw Hat gave me these dumplings!
فتى قبعة القش منحني هذه الدانغو
I will never... ever...
...أنا حتمًا... حتمًا
let them go to waste!
لن أُهدرها
There! You should see this too!
عليك مشاهدة هذا أيضًا
Why?! That's gramps...!
...لماذا العجوز
It serves him right! The same will happen to you if you cross us!
يستحق ذلك، هذا جزاء من يعارضنا
Keep that in mind!
تذكر ذلك
Now, the truth about the dumplings!
والآن، ابصق الدانغو
Which bonehead gave you those tickets?!
من الأحمق الذي كان يعطيك الإيصالات؟
I ate them!
ابتلعتها
How far do you think you can push me?
إلى أي مدى تريد استفزازي؟
I would rather die...
أفضّل الموت على إخبارك
...than tell a punk like you...!
أيها الوضيع
He answers the call of justice, uplifting the weak...
...إنه ذو خلق حسن ويساعد الضعفاء
without ever yielding to fools...
ولا يرضخ للحمقى أمثالكم
His is a truly chivalrous spirit,
...ذلك الرجل الشهم الشجاع
deserving of honor from my own chivalrous spirit, lest I dishonor myself!
عارٌ عليّ إن وشيت به ولم أقتدِ بشهامته
Now, kill me!
هيا اقتلني
Meeting him makes me nostalgic for a bygone era.
مقابلته ذكرتني بالأيام الخوالي
I am Hyogoro the Flower!
أنا هيوغورو الزهرة
For the first time in ages, my stomach and heart are full!
شعرتُ بالسعادة والشبع بعد مدة طويلة
This is a land of samurai!
هذه بلاد الساموراي
In the old days,
...في الماضي، كان يوجد رجال من طينته
many shared his spirit!
في كل أرجاء بلادنا
But you went and killed them all!
وأنتم قتلتموهم جميعهم
Hey!
مهلًا
Stop, Luffytaro!
توقف يا لوفيتارو
You know what happens when you defy the guards, right?!
أيها اللعين، ألا تعي عواقب عصيان أوامر الحراس؟
Kill me, you oaf!
اقتلني أيها الأحمق
What was that?! I dare you to say that again!
ماذا قلت؟ أتحداك أن تكرر ما قلته
I said that you are all brainless oafs who can't help but resort to violence!
إنكم حفنة من الحمقى طغيتم واستكبرتم والعنف عنوانكم
You're an oaf!
أيها الأحمق
Unfortunately, we failed to defeat you oafs.
ولكن لم نستطع التصدي لهؤلاء الحمقى
Right, since you said it again... I'm gonna kill you!
كررت ما قلته إذًا، سأقتلك
Stop! If you assault a guard,
...توقف، إن ضربت حارسًا
they'll execute you on the spot, Luffytaro!
فسيعدمونك فورًا يا لوفيتارو
Gramps!
أيها العجوز
Hey! No! Don't do it!
كلا، لا تفعلها
Stop!
توقف
Stop it...!
...توقف
You have... to stop...
لا يجب عليك فعلها
making me cry...!
عن جعلي أبكي
Master Daifugo!
دايفوغو-ساما
Anyone that attacks a guard is to be executed immediately!
كل من يعتدي على أحد الحراس مصيره الإعدام
We saw it this time! You can't weasel out of it!
رأينا الاعتداء هذه المرة، لا عذر لك
Kill him!
اعدموه
– Kill him! Kill him! Kill him!
اعدموه، اعدموه، اعدموه
Master Solitaire! The keys have been stolen!
سولتير-ساما، لقد سُرقت المفاتيح
Someone took a key for a pair of seastone cuffs!
سرق أحدهم مفاتيح أصفاد الحجر البحري
What are you clowns doing?! Didn't anyone see who did it?!
ماذا كنتم تفعلون يا أوغاد؟ هل رأى أحدكم الفاعل؟
A man with a big face crabbed them!
إنه رجل ذو وجه طويل-كاني
He got me to put a phony key in the safe.
طلب مني وضع مفتاح مزيف في الخزنة
I was tricked, crab it!
وانطلت عليّ حيلته-كاني
Since I can only walk sideways, he crabbed it right from under my nose!
استغل عجزي عن المشي إلا على جنب وسرق المفاتيح-كاني
You dolt!
أيها الوغد
You're an incompetent guard!
لا تصلح لأن تكون حارسًا
He must still be in the tower! Scour the place, including the attic!
لا بدّ أنه لم يخرج من البرج بعد، ابحثوا عنه حتى في العلية
This is the essence of a ninja!
هذه فائدة النينجا الحقيقية
I have the key!
حصلت على المفاتيح
Halt!
توقف
It's an intruder!
أيها الدخيل
Afterimages?!
ظل؟
Stop, thief!
توقف أيها المتسلل
It should have been sooner...!
من عساه سيتوقف في وضعٍ كهذا؟
Sir Luffytaro, just a little longer!
انتظرني يا لوفيتارو-دونو
It's time to escape!
حان وقت تحريرك
Now I just have to slip away stealthily!
لم يتبقّ سوى الهرب خلسة
His Awesomeness!
كوين-ساما
– Queen! Queen! Queen! Queen!
كوين، كوين، كوين، كوين
His Awesomeness, Superstar Queen, is here!
وصل النجم البارز كوين-ساما
Open the gate!
افتحوا البوابة
– Kill him! Kill him! Kill him! Kill him!
اعدموه، اعدموه، اعدموه، اعدموه
What's with the racket?
ما سبب هذه الضجة؟
It's so tragic...
...يسعدني ما فعله
There's no getting out of it this time!
ولكن يحزنني أنه لن يفلت هذه المرة
I won't forget you, Luffytaro!
لن أنساك يا لوفيتارو
This is the end for old man Hyo too!
حانت نهاية العجوز هيو أيضًا
You did great, Sir Straw Hat!
يا لها من ختامية عظيمة يا فتى قبعة القش
Why are you talking like it's over?!
ما بالك تتحدث وكأن نهايتنا حانت؟
Huh...?
سنهرب من هنا
It's no use! Don't resist!
لا فائدة، لا تقاوم
What can you do when you're weakened by seastone cuffs?!
ما الذي بوسعك فعله وأصفاد الحجر البحري تضعفك؟
Shut up...! If you wanna fight...
اخرسوا، إن أردتم القتال
bring it on!
هلمّوا إلي
What's the deal with that prisoner?
ما بال ذلك السجين؟
How is he able to fight so easily?
كيف يستطيع القتال بسهولة؟
Regulations state that the seastone cuffs shouldn't prevent the wearer from working.
تنص اللوائح على أنّ أصفاد الحجر البحري يجب ألّا تمنع مرتديها عن العمل
But his movements should still be severely impaired!
ولكن يُفترض أن تظل تحركاته ضعيفة للغاية
Are you saying that I'm still no match?!
أتقصد أنني لستُ ندًّا له؟
No, that's not what I meant!
كلا، لم أقصد ذلك
He's breathing heavily...
إنه يتنفس بصعوبة
Warden!
أيها الآمر
The seastone is working!
مما يؤكد تأثير أصفاد الحجر البحري عليه
He just has extraordinary resolve!
لكنه يتمتع بإرادة صلبة
It disturbs me how you're able to defy the laws of physics.
لن نرأف بشخص يخرق القوانين الأساسية في السجن
I consider it part of my training...
...أنا أتدرب حاليًّا
to become even a little bit stronger by the time I'm released from these!
لأصبح أقوى حين أتحرر من هذه الأصفاد
For someone without a future...
...ما الفائدة من تدريبك
what's the use in even trying?!
وأنت لن ترى شمس الغد أصلًا؟
Looks like I just found a sparring partner!
لِمَ لا تكون مشاركًا في تدريبي؟
You should know your place!
لا تغتر بنفسك
Let's see you withstand my elephant's sneeze!
استعد لهجمة من خرطوم فيلي
Elephant Achoo!
عطسة الفيل
Sir Straw Hat, are you okay?!
فتى قبعة القش، أما زلت حيًّا؟
Damn, he's strong!
تبًّا، يا لقوته
Warden Babanuki!
أيها الآمر بابانوكي
Superstar Queen arrived a bit ago!
وصل كوين-ساما قبل قليل
What?!
ماذا قلت؟
Why didn't you tell me sooner?!
لماذا لم تخبرني مسبقًا؟
If I get there before showtime, I'll kill you!
سأقتلك إن فاتني عرض كوين-ساما
I'm sorry!
أعتذر
Damn! If I could just use haki...
...سحقًا، لو كان بإمكاني فقط استخدام الهاكي
My sweet Komurasaki...
كوموراساكي-تان
You're so cute!
يا لظرافتك
Get excited!
أنا متحمس
She's too good for Orochi!
أوروتشي لا يستحق هذا الجمال
Komu-Womu... Komu-Womu...
...كومو-تان، كومو-تان
O-Oh, yeah...!
هذا صحيح
It's showtime.
حان وقت العرض
We'll stop by the pleasure hall later!
سنزور منطقة الملذات لاحقًا
Roger!
عُلم
When should we tell him Komurasaki died?
متى علينا إخباره بموت كوموراساكي؟
Never! We'd be the next ones to die!
لا يمكننا إخباره، سيقتلنا
Here we go!
لنبدأ
♪ Zoom, zoom, zoom, zoom! ♪
زوم، زوم، زوم، زوم
If I get thinner, I'll be too popular
إن نحفت سأصبح محبوبًا جدًّا
So I don't get thinner, that's my kind of...
...لذلك لا أفقد وزني، وذلك ما أدعوه
funk!
!فانك
♪ I may look chubby, but it's all muscle ♪
قد ترونها ترهلات لكنها عضلات
♪ I can sing and dance, that's my kind of... ♪
...بإمكاني الغناء والرقص، وذلك ما أدعوه
funk!
!فانك
Get excited!
تحمسوا
Thanks for waiting...
شكرًا على انتظاركم
you pieces of crap!
أيها الحثالة الأوغاد
Climb on!
اصعد على ظهري
O-Okay...!
حـ-حاضر
Now then...
والآن
Lay 'em on me one by one, Babanuki.
لنسمع ما عندك يا بابانوكي
Rank your biggest problems!
اسرد لي المشكلات من الأصغر للأكبر
Number three!
رقم ثلاثة
Eustass Kid escaped.
يوستاس كيد لاذ بالفرار
Number two!
رقم اثنان
The key to a pair of seastone cuffs has been stolen.
سُرقت مفاتيح أصفاد الحجر البحري
And number one!
رقم واحد
Straw Hat Luffy is on the run.
يحاول قبعة القش لوفي الهرب الآن
After him, you asshat!
اقبض عليه يا أحمق
Hey, it's no trouble whatsoever!
لا داعي للقلق بتاتًا
Feel free to use any of the empty houses!
امكثوا في أي منزل شاغر وعدّوه منزلكم
Anything for Young Master Zorojuro's friends!
خذوا راحتكم ما دمتم أصدقاء سيدي اليافع زوروجورو
Thanks.
اعذرنا
No need for gratitude.
لا عليك، فأهل القرية يموتون جوعًا واحدًا تلو الآخر
You really don't have to worry!
لا داعي للقلق حقًّا
How is that funny...?
ما المضحك؟
You sure laugh a lot.
إنك تضحك كثيرًا
When you're this hungry, all you have left is laughter!
ما على الجائع إلا الضحك
Anyway, you just missed the Young Master!
لو وصلتم أبكر قليلًا لصادفتم زوروجورو-سان
Where did he go?
أين ذهب؟
Well, he suddenly stormed out of here!
كل ما أعرفه أنه هرع فجأة من هنا
Said something about his sword getting stolen!
وقال إنّ سيفه سُرق
There's no telling how far he's run...
لم يخبرني أين سيبحث عنه
My money's on his getting lost on his way back...
لا بدّ أنه ضاع ولم يستطع العودة
As usual...
كالعادة
By the way, where did Black Leg go?
وأيضًا، لماذا الساق السوداء-يا ليس معنا هنا؟
When did we last see...?
...صحيح، لم أره منذ
That moron!
...لا بدّ أنه
The power of invisibility...
القدرة على الاختفاء
I guess I have to try it there...
ينبغي لي تجربتها هناك
By the way...
...الأهم
where's the bathhouse?
أيعرف أحدكم أين حمام النساء؟
Don't tell me...
...أيعقل أنه
he went there already!
ذهب سلفًا؟
It's so relaxing!
أشعر بالاسترخاء
So this is a Wanese bath?
هكذا تبدو حمامات بلاد وانو إذًا؟
But isn't it a little too hot?
ولكن أليست درجة حرارة المياه مرتفعة قليلًا؟
But it's classy to tolerate the heat and say, "The water is a bit chilly today."
أليس تحمّل هذه الحرارة أفضل  من الخروج قائلة "كان الحمام باردًا"؟
I guess I don't get the appeal...
لا أفهم هذا المنطق
Orobi, do you dislike the heat? Why don't you get into the hot water with us?
بالمناسبة، هل ضايقتك درجة الحرارة يا أوروبي؟ ألا تريدين الاستحمام؟
I'm not comfortable soaking in a public bathhouse.
لست مرتاحة بالاستحمام في حمام عام
If anything happens...
ماذا سنفعل لو حدث شيء؟
You're as cautious as a ninja!
أنتِ شديدة الحذر مثل النينجا
Magic users such as me and Orobi get weaker when we soak in water.
تضعف قوة السحرة أمثالنا أنا وأوروبي حين نستحم بسبب المياه
But you shouldn't worry! No foe will find us here.
ولكن اطمئني، لا أعداء هنا
They may not be foes, but...
...صحيح أنّ لا أعداء هنا، ولكن
Just look. Maybe I should charge them.
انظري، ألا يجدر بنا جعلهم يدفعون ثمن مشاهدتنا؟
I can't believe...
...لا أصدق
it's a mixed bath!
أنه حمام مختلط
Yes, it is.
أجل، هو كذلك
Have you never come across a mixed bathhouse like this?
أيعقل أنكِ لستِ معتادة على الاستحمام في حمام مختلط؟
Unsurprisingly, those men can't keep their eyes off me, but it can't be helped!
أعلم أنّ هؤلاء الرجال يحدقون في مفاتني، ولكن ما باليد حيلة
All young men love...
فلا يمكن للرجال مقاومة الإغراء
– Hey, move! – Old lady, you're in the way!
ابتعدي أيتها العجوز الشمطاء
Outta the way!
ابتعدي عن طريقنا
– Move! Move! Move!
ابتعدي، ابتعدي، ابتعدي
Ninpo: Ball Buster!
نينبو كينتاما تسوبوشي
Let's move to the washing area.
لنذهب إلى منطقة التدليك
When you're done warming up, you ask Sansuke to wash your back.
بعد مرحلة تدفئة الجسد، يحين دور سانسكي بتدليك الظهر
Who's Sansuke?
سانسكي؟ من هذا؟
He's Sansuke.
هذا سانسكي
It's what we call the one who washes our backs at the bathhouse.
إنه المتخصص بتدليك ظهور نزلاء الحمام
Why an octopus?
لماذا أخطبوط؟
Well, he has eight limbs, so he's suited to the job.
لأنه ملائم لهذه الوظيفة بصفته يملك ثمانية أطراف
Kyoshiro's one scary customer! Who knows what he was thinking...?
ولكن كيوشيرو مخيف، أجهل ما يفكر فيه
As if anyone knows what a yakuza thinks...
لأنه ياكوزا بالطبع
What're you talkin' about, you idiot?!
لا تهرف بما لا تعرف أيها المعتوه
Wano's yakuza are supposed to be for the people.
الوضع الطبيعي أن يكون الياكوزا في بلاد وانو حلفاء للشعب
Youngsters these days have no idea that there was once
...قد لا يعرف الشباب أمثالكم ذلك، ولكن في الماضي
a great yakuza boss named Hyogoro the Flower.
كان للياكوزا زعيم عظيم يدعى هيوغورو الزهرة
Is that the man Kanjuro mentioned?
أيقصد الرجل الذي أخبرنا كنجورو عنه؟
Twenty years ago, Wano's greatest yakuza boss...
...قبل عشرين سنة، أعظم زعيم ياكوزا في بلاد وانو كان يُدعى
was Hyogoro the Flower.
هيوغورو الزهرة
That's right. If Boss Hyogoro were still around,
فعلًا، إن كان الزعيم هيوغورو الزهرة موجودًا
he could've instantly rallied every last samurai.
لاستطاع توحيد كل الساموراي في صفنا فورًا
I honestly doubt we'll be able to recruit 5,000 by ourselves within the week.
لأصدقكما القول، ضم 5,000 ساموراي خلال أسبوع مستحيل
Maybe 500, at most.
ربما نضم 500 في أحسن الأحوال
Wow... He was that great?
هل كان عظيمًا إلى هذا الحد؟
He was!
أجل
Twenty years ago, he was the most influential man behind the scenes in Wano,
قبل عشرين سنة في بلاد وانو، كان له التأثير والنفوذ
the great boss who controlled the Flower Capital's underworld.
زعيم عظيم أخضع المجرمين في عاصمة الزهور
He had pull among the five regional bosses...
كانت كلمته مسموعة بين زعماء الياكوزا الخمسة الآخرين
and treated the common man well.
وطيبًا مع الشعب
He was a truly chivalrous yakuza with both power and charisma to boot.
كسب احترام الجميع بشهامته وقوته
Lord Oden himself grew up respecting him.
حتى أودين-ساما كان يحترمه في شبابه
Then, if we can find him...!
إذًا سيكون ذو عون لنا إن بحثنا عنه
It's been over twenty years.
مضت أكثر من عشرين سنة على ذلك
Rumor has it...
...وأيضًا ترددت الإشاعات
Orochi killed him for refusing to work under the Kurozumi Clan!
أنه رفض الانصياع لحكم عشيرة الكوروزومي، فقتله أوروتشي
He's the opposite of Fukurokuju, head of the Oniwabanshu.
وعلى النقيض، فوكوروكوجو قائد الأونيابانشو الذي كان يساند عشيرة الكوزكي مثل الزعيم هيوغورو الزهرة
but Fukurokuju chose to serve Orochi instead.
اختار الانصياع لحكم أوروتشي
I worked for him back then, but I couldn't take it and ran away.
غادرت فرقة النينجا التابعة لفوكوروكوجو لأنني لم أتقبل خيانته
Indeed, I became their enemy!
وأصبحتُ هاربة
I see...
فهمت
Is that you...
...أنت
Hanzo?!
هانزو
So you're alive! The man-seducing...
إذًا فأنتِ على قيد الحياة يا غاوية الرجال
sexy kunoichi.
الكونويتشي الجذابة
That's why Hanzo recognized you! You're so cool, Shinobu-chan!
اتضح الآن سبب معرفته بهويتك، ما أروعك يا شينوبو-تشان
I kind of am!
نوعًا ما
I miss that man...
...كم أفتقدك
Boss Hyogoro...
أيها الزعيم هيوغورو
He's become a part of history now...
أصبحت أسطورة متداولة
Tch...! You've given us a lot of trouble.
بئسًا، عكرت صفو مزاجنا بإثارتك للفوضى
Stop making me repeat myself...
لا تجبرني على تكرار كلامي
I'm telling you if you join our crew, Kaido will pardon you for everything!
كما أخبرتك، إن انضممت لطاقمنا فسيعفو كايدو-سان عن كل ما اقترفته
Shut up! I refuse!
اخرس، أرفض
What bad timing!
يا له من توقيت سيئ
Sir Luffy...!
لوفي-دونو
I have the key!
معي المفتاح
This is kind of nostalgic, Hyogoro!
ألا يذكرك هذا الحوار بالماضي يا هيوغورو؟
Kaido-san and Orochi eagerly approached you with a similar offer back then.
حين حاول كايدو-سان وأوروتشي ضمّك إلى صفوفنا بشدة
To think that legendary yakuza is now nothing but a malnourished old man.
أصبح الياكوزا الأسطوري مجرد عجوز يعاني من الجوع
And he'll die a miserable death!
وسيموت ميتةً مثيرة للشفقة
What? Is he the Hyogoro?
ماذا؟ هل قال هيوغورو؟
Get serious! That tiny old man?
محال، كيف يكون هو نفسه العجوز هيو؟
I don't care about myself...
لا يهمني مصيري
but please spare this young man!
ولكن أطلق سراح هذا الشاب
I'm begging you!
أتوسل إليك
Please!
أرجوك
What to do...?
ماذا أفعل؟
Okay, I've got it!
عظيم، حسمت قراري
I came up with an exciting idea!
خطرت ببالي فكرة مثيرة
Sir Luffy...!
...لوفي-دونو
I cannot believe it. You really do look the same as back then.
لا أصدق عيناي، لم تتغير منذ الأيام الخوالي
Who's that?!
من تكون؟
Is someone there?!
أيوجد أحد داخل الزنزانة؟
It is I, Raizo...
إنه أنا يا رايزو
Is Lord Momonosuke safe?
هل مومونوسكي-ساما بخير؟
Is that you...
...أيعقل أنك
Kawamatsu?!
كاواماتسو؟
Prisoner Mining Camp, Udon
منجم السجناء في أودون
m 760.5 808.5 l 1014 808.5 1014 973.5 760.5 973.5
m 726 784 l 798 974 1006 978 1012 812
Ringo
رينغو
Ebisu Town
بلدة إبيسو
Guard Alpacaman
ألباكامان حارس منجم السجناء - غيفتر مستخدم فاكهة سمايل ألباكا
Vice Warden Daifugo
دايفوغو نائب آمر منجم السجناء - شينوتشي مستخدم فاكهة سمايل العقرب
Vice Warden Solitaire
سولتير نائبة آمر منجم السجناء - شينوتشي مستخدمة فاكهة سمايل القرد
Warden Babanuki
بابانوكي آمر منجم السجناء - شينوتشي مستخدم فاكهة سمايل الفيل
Ebisu Town
بلدة إبيسو
A Bathhouse Flower Capital
حمام ساخن في عاصمة الزهور